generatorhostels.com 2019-10-15

# Privacy Policy - Stay Generator

## **GENERATOR HOSTELS SUMMARY PRIVACY NOTICE**

  1. ### **Who are we?**

Generator Hostels Ltd, (referred to as "Generator") is Europe’s fastest growing hostel brand located in the most central locations across Europe including Dublin, London, Copenhagen, Hamburg, Berlin, Venice, Barcelona, Paris, Amsterdam, Stockholm, Rome, Madrid and Miami.

Our head office address is: Generator Hostels Ltd, Venture House, 27-29 Glasshouse Street, London W1B 5DF. UK, United Kingdom.

The contact details for the companies that locally run our Group’s hostels, and who can help with any questions about your stay, are provided in the appendix of this document.

The full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice can be found at: Generator Hostels Privacy Notice

  1. ### **When do we collect personal data?**

We collect personal data when you 

  * Visit our Websites;
  * Use one of our Apps;
  * Make a booking on-line;
  * Contact our Reservation Centre or Guest Services Teams;
  * Provide payment details; or
  * Use our wi-fi provided by Air Angel;

For more information on wen we collect personal data please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice

  1. ### **Whose personal data do we collect?**

We collect customer’s personal data for: 

  * Individuals making bookings;
  * Guests;
  * Visitors;
  * Anyone calling one of our phone numbers; and
  * Business Contacts. 

We also process personal data for employees and business contacts. Employees should refer to Generator’s Employee Privacy Notice for details;

For more information on whose data we collect please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice.

  1. ###   **Why do we collect personal data?**

In most cases we collect and process personal information so that we can receive & respond to enquiries; make, amend & administer room bookings, process & store payment details, provide access to other products and services (such as meals), provide existing customers with information about our properties and to give them access to special offers and to gather customer feedback which helps us to improve the services that we offer and to improve our customers' experience whilst visiting or staying at one of our premises;

For more information on whose data we collect please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice.

  1. ### **What do we collect?**

It is necessary, in order for us to confirm and manage a reservation, that we collect personal data. This will include: 

  * Your name
  * Telephone or mobile number – in case of an emergency
  * Gender
  * Nationality
  * Date of Birth
  * Identification data i.e. Passport, Driving License details
  * In some instances, we request Credit card details, including the three-digit code that appears on the back of your credit card
  * Date of arrival and departure
  * Email address
  * We also require your credit card details to confirm your booking

  **Note:** Upon arrival we will require the same information from your fellow travellers, please ensure they are all aware of this to ensure a quick and efficient check-in.

For more information on the types of data we collect please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice.

  1. ### **How long do we keep your data?**

We keep personal data for different amounts of time based on our retention policies the type of data, reasonable periods during which we have a legitimate business interest to retain it and legal requirements. This is explained in more detail in our full privacy Policy summarised below: 

  * Customer personal data: 3 years;
  * Business Contact personal data: no more than 1 year following last use unless consent is for a longer period;
  * Employee personal data: as required by law

  1. ### **Direct Marketing**

Generator Hostels may use your data for marketing purposes, i.e. in order to inform you of its services which may, according to your past preferences, be of interest to you. These communications shall strictly adhere to applicable legal regulations.

Advertising and marketing materials of the Contracting or other parties shall be sent to you only if you opted in for these communications during the registration process, via e-mail or otherwise.

Your decision about direct marketing may be withheld in accordance with the opt-out rules described in each marketing e-mail or other form of communication. Opting out can be done via changing the settings of your User account or by directly contacting Generator Hostels (please see contact details below). Should you opt out, Generator Hostels shall retain only such data necessary for provision of services in accordance with the rules set out in this policy.

For more information on the processing that we undertake please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice.

  1. ### **Sharing of our personal data**

Your personal data shall not be shared or provided without your consent to any third party except in the following situations: (a) data is necessary for provision of services – for example credit card details will be exchanged with your bank for your booking to be confirmed (b) Generator Hostel’s is obliged to provide the personal data on the basis of law or upon order by a public authority, or (c) it is specifically allowed by applicable legal regulations.

For more information on when we may share your personal data shall not be shared with any third party please see the full Generator Hostels Privacy Notice.

  1. ### **Your Rights**

By submitting your information to us, you consent to the use of that information as set out in our full Privacy Policy. At any point while we are in possession of your personal data you have the following rights: 

  * You have the right to object to certain types of processing such as direct marketing;
  * You have the right to object to automated processing, including profiling;
  * You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you;
  * You have the right to ask us to correct the data that we hold about you that is inaccurate or incomplete;
  * In certain circumstances you can ask for the data we hold about you to be erased from our record;
  * Where certain conditions apply you have the right to ask that we restrict the processing of your personal data;
  * You may have the right to have the data we hold about you transferred to another organisation;
  * Right to judicial review: if Generator Hostels refuses your request under rights of access. Note: we will always provide you with a reason as to why we have refused your rights request;
  * You have the right to complain as outlined on the ICO Web Page:[ https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/your-personal-information-concerns/](http://https//ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/your-personal-information-concerns/)

**Note** : Rights requests will be forwarded on to a third party if one is involved in the processing of your personal data.

  1. ### **Data Security**

Generator Hostels will make every effort to ensure that your personal data is stored securely.  
The aim is to eliminate unauthorized or unlawful processing of your personal data, or accidental, unauthorized or unlawful access, use, transferring, processing, copying, transmitting, alteration, loss or damage of your personal data. Despite all efforts and meeting all rules set out by applicable legal regulations, it is not possible to guarantee the security of your data, if it is transferred or transmitted in an unsecured way.

For this reason, we have introduced adequate physical, technical and organizational measures and plans to protect and secure all information collected by our services using 

  * Using Cryptography, where necessary;
  * Using password protection, where necessary; and
  * Restricting access to your personal data (i.e. access to your personal data is granted only to those employees or personnel for whom the access is indispensable for the purposes described in this document and in our full privacy policy). 

We require that our partners, who provide supporting services that help us to store and otherwise process your personal data, apply the same high level of protection to your data.

**Note:** These measures do not remove your duty to secure your own personal data. You should, inter alia, regularly change your passwords and should never use predictable usernames and/or passwords, share your password with other persons, or grant access to your User account and/or disclose your personal data to other persons. 

  1. ### **Changes of Privacy Policy**

Generator shall, from time to time, change and update the terms of this Privacy policy. These changes will be posted at the url: https://staygenerator.com/information/privacy?lang=en-GB

  1. ### **Contact Details**

Should you wish to know more about Generator Hostels, its protection of your privacy, or about this Privacy policy, you can contact Generator Hostels at [dpo@staygenerator.com](mailto:dpo@generatorhostels.com)

Please help Generator Hostels ensure that your data is up-to-date. If you believe that some of the data processed by Generator Hostels is incorrect, please contact Generator Hostels at  
[dpo@staygenerator.com](mailto:dpo@generatorhostels.com).

  1. ### **Complaints**

Please contact Generator Hostels DPO on [dpo@staygenerator.com](mailto:dpo@generatorhostels.com) on if there is any data privacy and protection matter with which you are dissatisfied.

If you remain unhappy with the handling of your case, then you have the right to contact the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) as follows:

By phone (UK)0303 123 1113  
By phone (outside UK)+44 1625 545 700  
ICO Web Page - <https://ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint/your-personal-information-concerns/>  
Email: [dataprotectionfee@ico.org.uk](mailto:dataprotectionfee@ico.org.uk)

###   Anything else?

Please see our full privacy policy or contact our data protection officer on [dpo@staygenerator.com](mailto:dpo@generatorhostels.com) for any further information about how we protect your privacy.

## 

Company Registration

**GENERATOR HEAD OFFICE  
Company name: **Generator Hostels Ltd.  
**Office Address:  **Venture House, 27-29 Glasshouse Street, London W1B 5DF. UK  
**Registered Address:  **MacNaughton House, Compton Place, London WC1H 9SE. UK  
**Telephone number:  **+44 (0)207 432 7350  
**Fax:  **+44 (0)207 388 7644  
**Email:  **askus@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Registered in England  
**Registered number:  **3192617  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche and Alastair Thomann  
**VAT ID:  **GB 945 6083 04

**GENERATOR AMSTERDAM**  
****Company name:  ****Horizon Properties B.V.  
**Address:  **Mauritskade 57, 1092 AD, Amsterdam  
**Telephone number:  **+31207085600  
**Email:  **finance.amsterdam@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  ** Chamber of Commerce  
**Registered number:  **60538376  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:** NL853952590B01

**GENERATOR BARCELONA  
Company Name: **Generator BCN 1, S.L.  
**Address:  **Carrer de Corsega 373, 08037 Barcelona. Spain  
**Telephone number:  **+34 9322 00377  
**Email:** ask.barcelona@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **registered in Spain  
**Registered number:  **B65374811  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **ES B64888746

**GENERATOR BERLIN MITTE  
Company name: **Generator Berlin Mitte GmbH  
**Address:  **Oranienburger Str. 65, 10117 Berlin. Germany  
**Telephone number:  **+49 (0)30 92103 7680  
**Fax:  **+49 (0)30 27580 996  
**Email:  **ask.berlinmitte@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Amtsgericht Berlin Charlottenburg  
**Registered number:  **HRB 122701 B  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **DE 268310487

**GENERATOR BERLIN PRENZLAUER BERG  
Company name: **Generator Hostel Berlin GmbH  
**Address:  **Storkower Str. 160, 10407 Berlin. Germany  
**Telephone Number:  **+49 (0)30 417 2400  
**Fax:  **+49 (0)30 417 24080  
**Email:  **ask.prenzlauerberg@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Amtsgericht Berlin Charlottenburg  
**Registered address:  **Amtsgericht Berlin Charlottenburg  
**Registered number:  **HRB 83885  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:** DE 813 4097 37

**GENERATOR COPENHAGEN  
Company name: **Generator Hostel Copenhagen A/S  
**Address:  **Adelgade 5-7, 1304 Copenhagen, Denmark  
**Telephone number:  **+45 7877 5400  
**Email:  **ask.copenhagen@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **registered in Denmark  
**Registered number:  **32778097  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **DK 32778097

**GENERATOR DUBLIN  
Company name: **Generator Properties Dublin Ltd  
**Address:  **Smithfield Square, Dublin 7. Ireland  
**Telephone number:  **+353 1 901 0222  
**Email:  **ask.dublin@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Registered in Ireland  
**Registered address:  **Registered in Ireland  
**Registered number:  **480252  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **IE 9734900k

**GENERATOR HAMBURG  
Company name: **Generator Hostel Hamburg GmbH  
**Address:  **Steintorplatz 3, 20099 Hamburg, Germany  
**Telephone number:  **+49 (0)40 226 35 8460  
**Fax:  **+49 (0)40 226 35 8451  
**Email:  **ask.hamburg@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Amtsgericht Hamburg  
**Registered number:  **HRB 110518  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **DE 267 8330 80

**GENERATOR LONDON  
Company name: **Generator Hostel London Ltd.  
**Address:  **MacNaughton House, Compton Place, London WC1H 9SD. UK  
**Telephone number:  **+44 (0)207 388 7666  
**Fax:  **+44 (0)207 388 7644  
**Email:  **ask.london@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Registered in England  
**Registered number:  **2799205  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche and Alastair Thomann  
**VAT ID:  **GB 945 6083 04

**GENERATOR MADRID**  
****Company name:  ****Generator Hostel Madrid Ltd.  
**Address:  **Calle de San Bernardo 2, Madrid, Spain, 28013  
**Telephone number:  **+34 9104 79800  
**Email:** ask.madrid@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Registered in Spain  
**Registered number:  **A78484961  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  ** **ES-** A78484961

**GENERATOR MIAMI**  
**Company name:  **G 3120 Collins Operating Company LLC  
**Address:  **3120 Collins Avenue Miami Beach, Miami, USA, FL 33140  
**Telephone number:**  +1 786 496 5730  
**Email:  **miami@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:** Registered in USA  
**Registered number:** 35-2631523  
**Directors:** Andre Guettouche

**GENERATOR VENICE  
Company name: **Ghostell srl  
**Address:  **Fondamenta della croce 84-86, Isola della Giudecca, 30133 Venice, Italy  
**Telephone number:  **+39 (0)418778288  
**Email:  **ask.venice@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **registered in Italy  
**Registered number:  **VE-357882  
**Directors:** Benedetta Cattuzzo and Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **IT 04013800273

**GENERATOR ROME  
Company name: **Albergo Principe Amedeo srl  
**Address:  **Via Principe Amedeo, 257, 00185 Rome. Italy  
**Telephone number:  **+39 06 492330  
**Email:  **info@ambrapalacehotel.com or askus@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **Camera di Commercia, Roma, Italia  
**Registered number:  **04955750486  
**Directors:  **Benedetta Cattuzzo, ** ** Fabio Moccia and Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **IT 04955750486

**GENERATOR PARIS  
Company name: **Generator Hostels Paris Sas  
**Address:  **9-11 Place du Colonel Fabien, 75010 Paris. France  
**Tel:  **+33 (0)1 70 98 84 00  
**Email:  **ask.paris@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **registered in France  
**Registered number:  **2012 B15908  
**Directors:  ** Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **FR 83753023084

**GENERATOR STOCKHOLM  
Company name: **Generator Hostels Sweden AB  
**Address:  **Torsgatan 10, Stockholm, Sweden, 111 23  
**Tel:  **+46 (0)8 505 323 70  
**Email:** ask.stockholm@staygenerator.com  
**Registry:  **registered in Sweden  
**Registered number:  **559017-4404  
**Directors:  **Andre Guettouche  
**VAT ID:  **SE 559017440401
